Guide to the Samuel J. Tilden papers, 1794-1886 [bulk 1835-1876]
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series I. Correspondence, 1810 - 1919, n.d.; 38247; 35 boxes, 14.5 linear feet
  - I. B. General, 1830 - 1919, n.d.; 38280
    - Foley, John A., 1871 - 1875; 38710 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Foote, C. K., 1876; 38711 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Ford, Patrick, 1884; 38712 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Ford, Robert T., 1875; 38713 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Foster, J. W., 1864 - 1866; 38714 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Fowle, William B., undated; 38715 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Fowler, Isaac V., 1846 - 1867, n.d.; 38716 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Fowler, Thomas P., 1882; 38717 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Fowler, W., 1846; 38718 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Fowler, William A., 1879 - 1880; 38719 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Fowler, William J., 1875; 38720 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Fowler, William W., 1875; 38721 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Fox, John, 1875, 1882; 38722 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Francois, Alexander, 1876; 38723 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Fraser, Robert F., 1846; 38724 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - French, S. Bassett, 1875; 38725 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Friend, Joseph D., 1875; 38726 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Frost, Calvin, 1869; 38727 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Frott, Hermann, 1876; 38728 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Fuller, Melville W., 1868 - 1884; 38729 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Gale, H.D., 1874; 38730 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Gallaudet, Thomas, 1870, 1875; 38731 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Ganson, John, 1870; 38732 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Gardiner, O.C., 1853; 38733 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Gardiner, Thomas A., 1875; 38734 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Garland, Augustus Hill, 1884; 38735 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Garner, J. W., 1866; 38736 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Garnet, Henry Highland, 1876; 38737 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Garvin, S. B., 1872; 38738 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Gaston, William, 1877; 38739 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Gaylor, R., 1876; 38740 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - George, Henry, 1876; 38741 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Gerard, James W., 1846; 38742 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Gerry, Elbridge, 1872, 1875; 38743 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Getty, Robert P., 1870; 38744 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Gibbons, George W., 1875; 38745 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Gibson, A.M., 1879 - 1886; 38746 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Gibson, Randall L., 1876 - 1885; 38747 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Gilbert, Edward, 1864, 1877; 38748 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Gill, Fearing, 1882; 38749 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Gill, John, 1879; 38750 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Gillet, Ransom H., 1848 - 1861; 38751 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Gilmore, Quincey Adams, 1867 - 1874; 38752 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Godwin, Amil B., 1879; 38753 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Godwin, Parke, 1846, 1870 - 1883, n.d; 38754 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Goodell, J. G., 1861; 38755 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Goodell, R. E., 1877; 38756 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Gordon, John Brown, 1876, 1886; 38757 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Gordon, William J., 1864; 38758 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Gordon, William W., 1874 - 1875; 38759 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Gottsberger, William S., 1885 - 1886; 38760 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Goudy, C. H., 1870; 38761 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Gouge, William M., 1840 -1841, 1876; 38762 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Gould, Jacob, 1844 - 1846; 38763 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Gould, Jacob S., 1874 - 1875; 38764 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Gould, Jay, 1864 - 1883; 38765 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Gower, Franklin B., 1886; 38766 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Grace, William R., 1880; 38767 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Graham, D. Jr., 1846; 38768 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Grant, S. Hastings, 1874; 38769 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Grant, Ulysses S., 1876; 38770 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Gray, Neil, 1846; 38771 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Greeley, Horace, 1867 - 1872; 38772 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Green, Andrew E., 1851 - 1871; 38773 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Green, Andrew H., 1846 - 1875; 38774 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Green, Asabell, 1876; 38775 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Green, George, 1869, 1875; 38776 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Green, John A., 1868; 38777 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Green, Norvin, 1880, 1886; 38778 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Green, Lucy M., undated; 38779 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Greene, D. M., 1875, 1877; 38780 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Greatorex, Eliza, 1876; 38781 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Griffith, William R., 1853; 38782 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Griswold, John A., 1863 - 1864; 38783 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Griswold, W. D., 1859; 38784 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Groesbeck, William Slocum, 1884; 38785 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Gross, Magnus, 1879; 38786 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Gross, (First name unknown), 1884; 38787 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Grout, Paul, 1846; 38788 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Grover, Lafayette, 1885; 38789 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Grover, Martin, 1847, 1869 - 1870; 38790 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Guion, Clement, 1841, 1846, 1875; 38791 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Gunther, Charles Godfrey, 1877; 38792 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Gurney & Sons, 1864; 38793 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Guthrie, James, 1860, 1862; 38794 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Gwin, William M. {1863 - 1876, 38795 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Hackett, John K., 1863 - 1876; 38796 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Hadley, John L., 1872; 38797 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Haines, John H., 1861; 38798 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Haines, John P., 1886; 38799 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Hall & Buell, 1886; 38800 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Hall, Charles M., 1875; 38801 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Hall, A. Oakey, 1859 - 1872, n.d.; 38802 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Hall, John, 1882 - 1883; 38803 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Hall, L. W., 1845; 38804 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Hall, Parris, 1877; 38805 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Halpine, Charles G., 1860 - 1865; 38806 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Halsey, Gaius Leonard, 1875; 38807 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Hamilton & Parry, 1846; 38808 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Hamilton, Alexander Jr., 1854; 38809 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Hammers, S. S. W., 1881 - 1882; 38810 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Hammond, L. H., 1875; 38811 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Hampton, Wade, 1877; 38812 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Hance, James, 1845, 1876; 38813 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Hancock, Winfield Scott, 1868 - 1880; 38814 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Hand, Samuel, 1875 - 1880; 38815 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Hand, Stephen D., 1831 - 1833; 38816 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Hanna, B. W., 1885; 38817 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Hanscomb, A. H., 1846; 38818 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Hardin, C. H., 1876; 38819 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Harmon, John Henry, 1876; 38820 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Harrington, George, 1862; 38821 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Harris, Ira, 1862; 38822 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Harris, Phillip P., 1877; 38823 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Harrisse, Henry, 1876; 38824 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Harrison, Burton, 1872 - 1876; 38825 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Hart, Emanuel B., 1846, 1857, 1886; 38826 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Hart, J. C., 1846; 38827 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Hart, William T., 1864; 38828 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Haswell, Charles H., undated; 38829 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Hatch, Israel Thompson, 1856; 38830 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Hathorn & Southgate, 1872; 38831 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Hatton, O. C., 1875; 38832 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Havemeyer, Henry, 1878 - 1879, n.d.; 38833 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Havemeyer, William F., 1845 - 1874, n.d.; 38834 (Box 13, Folder 47)
      1845 letter not positively identified; may have been written to Benjamin F. Butler.
    - Hawley, John B., 1879; 38835 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Hawley, Joseph R., 1886; 38836 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Hawley, Seth C., 1875, 1879; 38837 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Hawley, William S., 1868; 38838 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Hay, John Campbell, 1865, 1874 - 1875; 38839 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Hayden, M. W., 1885; 38840 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Hazard, Rowland Gibson, 1867; 38841 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Hearst, Charles H., 1860; 38842 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Hedges, Thomas A., ca. 1853; 38843 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Hedges, Miss (First name unknown), undated; 38844 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Helper, Hinton Rowan, 1868; 38845 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Hendee, Richard S., 1859; 38846 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Henderson, Isaac, 1864, 1874; 38847 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Hendricks, Thomas A., 1876; 38848 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Henry, Joshua J., 1860; 38849 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Henry, R. H., 1884; 38850 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Herrick, Anson, 1858, n.d.; 38851 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Herring, William, 1875; 38852 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Hewitt, Abram S., 1863 - 1883, n.d.; 38853 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - Hibbard, T. R., 1846; 38854 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Hill, Benjamin H., 1880; 38855 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Hill, David Bennett, 1870 - 1886; 38856 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Hill, Nicholas, 1856; 38857 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Hilliard, O.G., 1864; 38858 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Hilliard, G.S., 1860; 38859 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Hilton, Henry, 1866; 38860 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Hitchcock, J. R., 1875; 38861 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Hitchcock, Phineas W., 1858 - 1875; 38862 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Hitchcock, Thomas, 1881; 38863 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Hitchcock, (First name unknown), 1859; 38864 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Hoadley, George, 1876 - 1885; 38865 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Hobart, Garret H., 1878; 38866 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Hobart, L. Smith, 1883; 38867 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Hoe, Annie L., 1883; 38868 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Hoes, John Van Allen, 1834; 38869 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Hoffman, John T., 1861 - 1875, n.d.; 38870 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Hogeboom, Charles L., 1875; 38871 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Hogeboom, Henry H., 1846, 1863; 38872 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Hogeboom, Tobias, 1845; 38873 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Holbrook, Edwin M., 1876; 38874 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Holden, J.P.G., 1876; 38875 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Homans, J. Smith, 1861; 38876 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Homer, Peter T., 1846; 38877 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Honig, Isaac, 1876; 38878 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Hooker, John, 1876; 38879 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Hoover, J.D., 1868; 38880 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Hopkins, Francis, 1875; 38881 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Hopkins, Nelson K., 1874 - 1875; 38882 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Houghton, Vas, 1875; 38883 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Howe, Samuel O., 1866 - 1885; 38884 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Howell, Clark, 1884; 38885 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Howell, Evan P., 1885; 38886 (Box 14, Folder 35)
      See also: Clark Howell
    - Howlett, H. R., 1846; 38887 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Hoyt, Colgate, 1886; 38888 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Hoyt, John W., 1885; 38889 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Hoyt, L., 1848; 38890 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Hoyt, M., 1845; 38891 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Hudson, Charles, 1875; 38892 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Huey, James Buchanan, 1875; 38893 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Hughes, Charles, 1874; 38894 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Hughes, F. W., 1875 - 1876; 38895 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Humphrey, J., 1868; 38896 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Hunt, Louise Livingston, 1875 - 1885; 38897 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Hunt, Ward, 1848, 1875; 38898 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Hunt, Wilson G., 1868, 1876; 38899 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Hunter, John, 1876; 38900 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Hunter, John W., 1875; 38901 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Hunter, William Jr., 1876; 38902 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Huntington, D., 1875 - 1883; 38903 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Hunton, Eppa, 1878 - 1879, n.d.; 38904 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Hurlburt, William H., 1863 - 1882, n.d.; 38905 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Hutchings, Marie I., 1880; 38906 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Hutchings, Robert, 1872, 1876; 38907 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Hutchins, Stilson, 1875, 1880; 38908 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Hutchinson, Charles W., 1875; 38909 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Hyatt, Stephen, 1846; 38910 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Ingersoll, Colin MacRae, 1868 - 1878; 38911 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Independent Order of Oddfellows, 1845; 38912 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Iron City Tilden Club, 1879; 38913 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Ireland, J. Edward, 1883; 38914 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Irving, Richard, 1859; 38915 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Irwin, William, 1876; 38916 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Ives, M., undated; 38917 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Jackson, H. J., 1874 - 1875; 38918 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Jackson, James, 1827; 38919 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Jacques, William Henry, 1886; 38920 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      See also: Coastal defense; James Carlisle, John Newton, Samuel Randall.
    - James, C. M., 1875; 38921 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Janes, M. E., 1859; 38922 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Jarvis, Nathaniel, 1843 - 1846; 38923 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Jarvis, Thomas J., 1879; 38924 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Jenkins, J. M., 1874; 38925 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Jenks, George A., 1885; 38926 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Jernigan, L., 1866; 38927 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Jerome, Leonard W., 1879, 1875, n.d; 38928 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Jervis, John B., 1846, 1875; 38929 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Jewett, Sarah B., 1855 - 1856, 1878 - 1884, n.d; 38930 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Johnson, Andrew, 1866 - 1868; 38931 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Johnson, C., ca. 1844; 38932 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Johnson, C. S., 1859; 38933 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Johnson, Reverdy, 1863; 290675 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Johnson, S.C., 1880; 38934 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Johnson, S. M., 1868; 38935 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Johnson, William, 1868; 38936 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Johnson, J. S., 1881; 38937 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Jones, Aquilla, 1871; 38938 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Jones, Aurelia Anna, 1841; 38939 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Jones, E. F., 1874; 38940 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Jones, George, 1871, 1884; 38941 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Jones, Isaac, 1827; 38942 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Jones, J. D., undated; 38943 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Jordan, Conrad N., 1882 - 1886; 38945 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Julian, George W., 1879 - 1885; 38946 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Kalbfleisch, Martin, 1863, 1875; 38947 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Keep, Henry, 1855; 38948 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Kellog, Charles D., 1885; 38949 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Kellog, John D., 1846; 38950 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Kelly, John, 1859 - 1875; 38951 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Kelly, Sherman, 1860 - 1871; 38952 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Kelsey, Henry C., 1886; 38953 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Kemble, G., 1871; 38954 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Kemble, William, 1875; 38955 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Kennaday, John R., 1875; 38956 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Kennedy, Joseph Camp Griffith, 1863; 38957 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Kennedy, John S, 1864; 38958 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Kern, J., 1841; 38959 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Kernan, Francis, 1866 - 1879; 38960 (Box 15, Folder 50-53)
    - Kernan, Nicholas, 1875 - 1876; 38961 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Kerr, M. C., 1872; 38962 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Ketchum, Hiram, 1860 - 1868; 38963 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Ketchum, John W., 1876; 38964 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Kettell, Thomas P., 1845 - 1846; 38965 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Killey, E. B., 1846; 38966 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Kimball, C. P., 1875; 38967 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Kimball, J. P., 1876; 38968 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Kimmond, W., 1864; 38969 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - King, J. Floyd, 1883 - 1886; 38970 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - King, Preston, 1845 - 1862, n.d.; 38971 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - King, Rufus, 1831; 38972 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Kingsley, William C., 1874 - 1878; 38973 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Knapp, J. G., 1831 - 1832; 38974 (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Knox, Henry E., 1857, 1880; 38975 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Knox, John Jay, 1875 - 1878; 38976 (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Lacombe, Emile Henry, 1878; 38977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Lafitte, John B., 1876; 38978 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Laflin, A. H., 1875; 38979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Lambert, Edward, 1876; 38980 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Lamont, Daniel S., 1871 - 1885; 38981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Landon, M.D., 1868; 38982 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Lang, Charles M., 1886; 38983 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Langtree, Miss, 38984 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Lanier, Charles, 1862 - 1884; 38985 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Laning, Albert P., 1866; 38986 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Lanphier, Charles H., 1885; 38987 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Lapham, George H., 1876; 38988 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Laporte, John, 1848; 38989 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Latham, R. W., 1868; 38990 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Lathers, Richard, 1877; 38991 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Lathrop, F. A., 1876; 38992 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Laurence, M., 1846; 38993 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Lawrence, A. R., 1859 - 1871; 38994 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Lawrence, Joseph, undated; 38995 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Lawrence, William Beach, 1871 - 1877; 38996 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Ledyard, John, 1844; 38997 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Lee, Mrs. Fitzhugh, 1875; 38998 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Lee, Frederick, 1847; 38999 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      On behalf of the Democratic Republican Judicial Convention.
    - Lee, Leonard, 1843, 1846; 39000 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Leitch, John M., 1870; 39001 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Leslie, Frank, 1875 - 1976; 39002 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Lester, C. Edwards, 1858; 39003 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Leverett, Josiah S., 1838; 39004 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Levy, Jefferson M., 1882 - 1883; 39005 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Levy, S.S., 1873; 39006 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Lewis, D. B., 1868; 39007 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Lewis, E. B., 1879; 39008 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Lieberman, Henry, 1864; 39009 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Lieb, Herman, 1885; 39010 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Lincoln, Abraham, 1861; 39011 (Box 16, Folder 35)
      Draft of letter from Tilden in support of Noah Swayne.
    - Litchfield, Edwin C., 1860, 1875; 39012 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Lloyd, Henry D., 1872; 39013 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Lockwood, Gersh, 1881; 39014 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Lombard, Katrina, 1881; 39015 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - London, Daniel H., 1874; 39016 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Long, Alexander, 1880, 1885; 39017 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Loomis, A., 1870 - 1878; 39018 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Lord, Scott, 1875 - 1876; 39019 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Lothrop, George V. N., 1878 - 1879; 39020 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Lott, John A., 1869, 1874 - 1875; 39021 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Louisville Cultural Exposition, 1878; 39022 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Low, Henry R., 1886; 39023 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Lowell, Josephine Shaw, 1876, 1882 - 1885; 39024 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Lowry, R. B., 1876; 39025 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Ludington, Harrison, 1876; 39026 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Ludlow, William Handy, 1856 - 1858; 39027 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Lunt, George, 1868 - 1884; 39028 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Lynch, Anne Charlotte, 1852, undated; 39029 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - McCagg, E. B., 1862; 39030 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Mace, J. Ellis Jr., 1877; 39031 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - McClellan, George B., 1873 - 1877; 39032 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - McClellan, Robert, 1838 - 1857; 39033 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - McClelland, John A., 1876 - 1886; 39034 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - McCloskey, Felix, 1885; 39035 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - McCloskey, Lawrence W., 1878, 1886; 39036 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - McCook, George W., 1868 - 1875, n.d.; 39037 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - McCoppin, Frank, 1885; 39038 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - McCormic, Cyrus H, 1874 - 1884; 39039 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - McCreary, James B., 1879 - 1885; 39040 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - McCullough, Hugh, 1964 - 1886, n.d; 39041 (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - McCullough, James N., 1878; 39042 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - McCunn, John H., 1867; 39043 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - McCurdy, R. H., 1861, 1864, 1875; 39044 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - McDonald, J. E., 1868 - 1876; 39045 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - McElroy, C. T., 1885; 39046 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - McGill, Alexander T., 1880; 39047 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - McGreal, Thomas J., 1885; 39048 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - McHenry, James, 1884; 39049 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - McHugh, James V., 1886; 39050 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - MacIver, D. and C., 1881; 39051 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - McKee, David R., 1886; 39052 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - McKelvey, St. Clair, 1878 - 1879; 39053 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - McKenna, Charles, 1880; 39054 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - McKeon, John, 1857, 1868, 1880; 39055 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - McKibben, J., 1868; 39056 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Mackin, James, 1876; 39057 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - McKnight, D. A. W., 1885; 39058 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - McLane, Allan, 1869; 39059 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - McLane, Robert M., 1868 - 1885; 39060 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - McLaren, D., 1872; 39061 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - McLaughlin, Hugh, 1875 - 1876, 1885 - 1886; 39062 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - McLean, Charles F., 1864; 39063 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Maclean, Charles H, 1874 - 1875; 39064 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Maclean, Edward P., 1874 - 1876; 39065 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - McLean, Washington, 1868 - 1870; 39066 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - McMahon, J.A., 1876; 39067 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - MacMillan, A. K., 1883; 39068 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - McMurray, William, 1845; 39069 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - McVickar, W.H., 1857 - 1859; 39070 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Magann, E. W., 1879; 39071 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Magone, Daniel Jr., 1868 - 1885; 39072 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Mangin, John, 1886; 39073 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Manhattan Club, 1876, 1880; 39074 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Mann, A. Jr., 1846; 39075 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Mann, George S., 1844 - 1846; 39076 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Manning, A. R., 1876; 39077 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Manning, Daniel, 1868 - 1886, n.d.; 39078 (Box 17, Folder 34-38)
    - Marble, Manton, 1871 - 1885; 39079 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Marbury, F. F., 1846, 1875; 39080 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Marcy, William Learned, 1845 - 1854, n.d.; 39081 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Marsh, Ebenezer S., 1855; 39082 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Marsh, Luther R., 1859; 39083 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Marshall, Charles H., 1846, 1873 - 1875, 1885; 39084 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Marshall, D.D.T., 1846, 1875; 39085 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Marshall, Stephen S., 1875; 39086 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Martin, M. L., 1857; 39087 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Martin, Mattias, 1848; 39088 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Martin, W. R., 1881; 39089 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Maryland State Agricultural & Mechanical Association, 1878; 39090 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Mason, C., 1846; 39091 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Mason, Charles, 1864; 39092 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Mason, J. M., 1860; 39093 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Mather, Samuel L., 1871; 39094 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Mathews & Longyear, 1878; 39095 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Matsell, George W., 1857, 1875; 39096 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Matthews, James, 1879; 39097 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Matthews, Stanley, 1871; 39098 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Maurice, James, 1886; 39099 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Maxwell, Hugh, 1846; 39100 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Maynard, A. B., 1881; 39101 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Maynard, M. H., 1883, 1885; 39102 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Meade, Edwin R., 1872 - 1886; 39103 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Meade, Nathan B., 1875; 39104 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Melville, Gansevoort, 1844; 39105 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Merrick, R. T., 1862 - 1885; 39106 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Messler, Thomas D., 1866 - 1867; 39107 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Meyer, E., 1876; 39108 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Miggal, Edward, 1875 - 1877; 39109 (Box 18, Folder 23)